i don't wanna fall in love right now
i'll take you for a ride
if you wanna get down
i don't wanna fall in love with you
i'll take you for a ride
if you really want to
i'll give you what you need,
and that's a guarantee
but girl, you best believe,
don't fall in love with me
i don't wanna fall in love right now
i'll take you for a ride
if you wanna get down
boom, who is that chick
that i was talking to?
shorty kinda bad,
i really like the view
she look at me like that,
i think she want me too
you know i gotta ask,
i got nothing else to lose
can you tell me where you at,
and what's your next move?
you could do the math,
what you think we gonna do?
i'ma bring you back
and i'll take you to my room
shorty, do you wanna come through?
i don't wanna fall in love right now
i'll take you for a ride
if you wanna get down
i don't wanna fall in love with you
i'll take you for a ride
if you really want to
i'll give you what you need,
and that's a guarantee
but girl, you best believe,
don't fall in love with me
i don't wanna fall in love right now
i'll take you for a ride
if you wanna get down
i wanna do ya,
i'll give it to ya
i'ma make you scream in pain
i don't need to know your name
let's get into it,
i wanna do it
we don't need to be in love
i'ma tear your ass up
i wanna do ya,
i'll give it to ya
come over right damn now
i'ma turn the lights out
i like it freaky,
so come and tease me
let me give it to you right now
face down
i don't wanna fall in love right now
i'll take you for a ride
if you wanna get down
i don't wanna fall in love with you
i'll take you for a ride
if you really want to
i'll give you what you need,
and that's a guarantee
but girl, you best believe,
don't fall in love with me
i don't wanna fall in love right now
i'll take you for a ride
if you wanna get down